### **[Podcast Republic](https://podcastrepublic.net/)**

### Privacy

This policy applies to all information collected or submitted on Podcast Repulic’s website and our apps for Android and any other devices and platforms.

#### Information we collect

When creating an account, you will be asked to enter an optional email address and a password, or through Google login service. Email addresses are only used for logging in, password resets, responding to emails that you initiate, and notifications that you request. We don’t send promotional emails.

When rating a podcast or leaving a review for a podcast, an unique device ID will be stored to track the review for editing/deleting purposes. This unique device is also needed to combat fraud and abuse. This unique device ID won't be shared with any third parties.

We store information about your podcasts, radio stations, episodes, and listening progress to sync this information between the website and your devices. We also collect anonymous statistics about which podcasts are most popular to help inform our recommendation engine.

The Podcast Republic’s Android app uses third party services that may collect inforaction used to idenfity you. Main third party services used includes Google Play services, YouTube Data API, etc.

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by Podcast Republic’s Android app

#### Information usage

We use the information we collect to operate and improve our website, apps, and customer support.

We do not share personal information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to accomplish Podcast Repulic functionality. We may share anonymous, aggregate statistics with outside parties, such as how many people listen to a particular podcast with Podcast Repulic.

We may disclose your information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal requirements; to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or abuse, violations of our policies; or to protect our rights and property.

#### Log Data

We want to inform you that whenever you use Podcast Republic’s Android app, in a case of an error in the app we may collect data and information on your device called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, information about your podcasts, radio stations, episodes, and listening progress and other statistics. The Log Data will be stored on your device. The Log Data will not be shared with any kind of third party service without your consent.

#### Third-party links and content

Podcast Repulic displays links and content from third-party podcast feeds and sites, and downloads podcast files directly from each podcast’s third-party servers. These have their own independent privacy policies, and we have no responsibility or liability for their content or activities.

#### Security

We implement a varity of security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please be aware that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Accessing, changing, or deleting your information

You may access or change your information or delete your account from the Podcast Repulic Android app.

Deleted information may be kept in backups for up to 90 days. Backups are encrypted and are only accessed if needed for disaster recovery.

#### Information Relating to Children

Podcast Repulic is not intended for children under age 13, or for anyone under age 18 or the applicable age of majority without involvement of a parent or guardian. We do not knowingly collect or distribute personal information from or about children under the age of 13.

#### Use of Information Outside Your Country of Residence

By using Podcast Repulic and providing your information, you authorize us to collect, use, and store your information outside of the European Union.

If you choose to use the Podcast Repulic’s app or our site or provide your information to us, your information may be transferred to, processed and maintained on servers or databases located outside of the country or jurisdiction where you are located. Your use of the Podcast Repulic app or the our site represents your consent and agreement to these practices.

#### International Transfers of Information

Information may be processed, stored, and used outside of the country in which you are located. Data privacy laws vary across jurisdictions, and different laws may be applicable to your data depending on where it is processed, stored, or used.

#### Your Consent

By using our site or apps, you consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms and conditions.

#### Privacy Policy Updates

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

### Terms & Conditions

#### Warranty, Disclaimer and Indemnity

PODCAST REPUBLIC PROVIDES THE APP AND THE SITE “AS IS” AND WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, AND PODCAST REPUBLIC HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, COMPATIBILITY, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. YOUR USE OF THE APP AND SITE AND ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE APP AND SITE IS AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR OTHER DEVICE OR LOSS OF DATA, LOST PROFITS OR REVENUE THAT DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY RESULTS FROM SUCH USE. You agree to indemnify and hold harmless PODCAST REPUBLIC from any and all claims, demands, damages, losses, liabilities, costs, and expenses (including attorney’s fees) arising from Your use of the APP and the SITE.

#### Limitation of Liability

UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES (AND UNDER NO LEGAL THEORY, TORT, CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE) SHALL PODCAST REPUBLIC, ITS AFFILIATES, LICENSORS OR SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PERSON FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY CHARACTER, EVEN IF FORESEEABLE, INCLUDING COST OF SUBSTITUTE TECHNOLOGY, DAMAGES FOR LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF GOODWILL, WORK STOPPAGE, ACCURACY OF RESULTS, LOSS OF DATA, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION. NOTHING IN THIS AGREEMENT WILL EXCLUDE OR LIMIT EITHER PARTY’S LIABILITY IN RESPECT OF: (A) DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY CAUSED BY THE NEGLIGENCE OF THAT PARTY; (B) FRAUD (INCLUDING FRAUDULENT MISREPRESENTATION); OR (C) ANY LIABILITY WHICH MAY NOT OTHERWISE BE LAWFULLY EXCLUDED OR LIMITED.
